ropeofsilicon.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy - RopeofSilicon.com

| 

Overview

RopeofSilicon.com considers the protection of personal privacy to be one of our most important values. This privacy policy ("Policy") gives you specific information on how we protect your privacy, how we treat personal information, and the choices you have. 

This Policy applies to RopeofSilicon.com and all its services. Please note that this Policy applies only to RopeofSilicon.com and services maintained by RopeofSilicon.com and not to web sites or services provided by other companies or organizations to which we link. 

As a condition of using RopeofSilicon.com, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy. Additional terms and conditions which govern your use of RopeofSilicon.com are contained in our User Agreement, and, as applicable, in certain other service specific license agreements or terms of use, which you will be notified of at the time of your registration for the applicable services. 

The Policy is accessible through RopeofSilicon.com in several ways, including from a link entitled "Privacy Policy" at the bottom of just about every RopeofSilicon.com page. You acknowledge that this Policy may change over time. You should check RopeofSilicon.com regularly for any changes to this Policy and our Terms of Use. Your continued use of RopeofSilicon.com will signify that you agree to these changes. 

Children

RopeofSilicon.com is **not** directed to children under the age of 13. RopeofSilicon.com will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13. 

**NOTE TO PARENTS:** If you have any concerns about RopeofSilicon.com or the services we offer, please contact us via our online form available at http://www.ropeofsilicon.com/contactus/. RopeofSilicon.com encourages parents to spend time online with their children. We also urge parents to instruct their children never to give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers without parental permission when using the Internet. 

Information Collection, Storage and Use

We refer to information that identifies an individual as "Personal Information". In general, RopeofSilicon.com collects Personal Information from users of RopeofSilicon.com in connection with access to certain online areas or services, including during (i) registration for certain online community services; (ii) registration for special communications, such as email updates, email alerts and newsletters; (iii) subscription registration; (iv) events, sweepstakes, contests or promotions; (v) online user polls, quizzes and other interactivity. Your Personal Information is stored on RopeofSilicon.com computer servers located in the United States. 

We may gather data about the areas of RopeofSilicon.com you visit or access. We do not use any of this navigational data about where you "as an individual user" go on RopeofSilicon.com or share any of this data with third parties. However, we do use and share navigational data in aggregate, non-personal form to understand how users, as a group, use and navigate RopeofSilicon.com. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in public areas of RopeofSilicon.com, such as the member home pages, RopeofSilicon.com forums, User Reviews and Comments in relation to movies, news articles, etc. your information can be viewed and possibly used by others. We advise users to be especially careful in such public areas about disclosing Personal Information, such as full name, home address, credit card information or phone number. 

Below are more details about the Personal Information we, or third parties may gather from you and how we may use it. 

**A. Email Newsletters and Alerts.** RopeofSilicon.com offers email newsletters and subscription based email alerts to its registered members. We will use your email address to send you only the specific newsletter(s) and alert(s) that you signed up for. If you want to update your email address or stop receiving a newsletter, follow the procedures to unsubscribe at the bottom of any newsletter or alert you receive or simply visit Your User Homepage to update your profile and email subscriptions. 

**B. Membership Information.** When you register for a membership at RopeofSilicon.com, we will ask you for certain minimum required information, such as your name, birth date, gender, email address and zip code. We may also ask for additional information about you and your interests. We do this so we can better understand your preferences and tailor RopeofSilicon.com to suit you better. The more information you volunteer, the more we can tailor the RopeofSilicon.com Site and promotions to your interests. Additionally, third party service providers may require you to assent to their privacy policy as a condition to receiving their service. 

**· Advertisers.** RopeofSilicon.com may send you emails on behalf of our advertisers. If you opt to receive information from our advertisers they may use your Personal Information to send you advertisements or other notices, via email or postal mail, and it is possible that your information may be shared with others. Please read any and all correspondence carefully and take proper measures to ensure your privacy. 

**C. Email Updates to Members.** If you so elect at registration, we may periodically send you promotional email about products or services offered by RopeofSilicon.com, our partners and advertisers. If you want to update your email address or stop receiving these types of promotional emails, please follow the procedures to unsubscribe at the bottom of any email we send you or simply visit Your User Homepage to update your profile. 

We may contact you regarding account status, changes to this Policy, our User Agreement or other terms of use, to confirm your registration or for any other business reason related to your use of RopeofSilicon.com. 

**D. Promotions.** We may ask you for Personal Information at other times, including, but not limited to, when you enter sweepstakes, contests or promotions sponsored by RopeofSilicon.com or a third party. If you choose to enter sweepstakes, contests or promotions sponsored by a third party, the Personal Information you provide will be subject to the privacy policy of the third party sponsor. We encourage you to check the applicable third party policy before providing any Personal Information. 

**E. Surveys and User Research.** RopeofSilicon.com conducts email and web-delivered surveys from time to time, as well as instant polls, to gather information about our users. Taking these surveys and polls is entirely optional. You have no obligation to respond to them. We share only the aggregate results of these surveys, not Personal Information, with our advertisers and partners to help them better understand our services and monitor the reach of their advertising or other offerings on our service. We also use some of the Personal Information that you provide in these surveys to help us understand your interests and to make RopeofSilicon.com more useful to you. 

**F. Use of Cookies.** On the Internet, a "cookie" is a piece of information (a file) that a Website transfers to a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common on the Internet. The process used to serve advertisements and to track use of RopeofSilicon.com involves cookies. 

RopeofSilicon.com uses third party advertising companies (i.e. Gorilla Nation Media) to display advertisements on RopeofSilicon.com. These advertisements will most likely contain cookies, however RopeofSilicon.com has no access to any Personal Identifiable Information collected via these cookies. 

A cookie may also be placed on your computer when logging in to RopeofSilicon.com, allowing the site to remember your log-in information the next time you visit RopeofSilicon.com. 

You may configure your browser to reject cookies, but this may interfere with some functionality of RopeofSilicon.com. To find out more about cookies, we suggest the All About Cookies Site located at [allaboutcookies.com](http://www.allaboutcookies.com/). 

**G. Sites You Visit.** As you access and browse around RopeofSilicon.com, RopeofSilicon.com may store information about which pages you visit and other information presented in your browser's URL address line. RopeofSilicon.com will use this information to help determine what our users are most interested in. 

**H. Sharing Non-Personal Information.** RopeofSilicon.com may share information that is not Personal Information -- meaning non-personal, aggregate, or summary, information regarding our users -- with other third parties not mentioned in this Policy. This kind of information does not identify you individually. 

**I. Merger or Acquisition.** In the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of all or substantially all of its assets, or the sale of an individual website owned by RopeofSilicon.com, RopeofSilicon.com may transfer your Personal Information to a third party as a part of such merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale. 

**J. Legal Authorities.** RopeofSilicon.com may also disclose Personal Information in cases when we reasonably believe that it is necessary to identify someone who may be violating RopeofSilicon.com policies, RopeofSilicon.com [User Agreement](http://www.ropeofsilicon.com/useragreement/) or other terms of use, or who may be a threat to RopeofSilicon.com or third party rights, property, or personal safety. RopeofSilicon.com may disclose Personal Information to comply with valid legal process such as a duly issued search warrant, subpoena or court order. 

Access to Other Sites through RopeofSilicon.com

**Linking to Other Sites.** You may visit independent web sites, not owned or operated by RopeofSilicon.com, through links on RopeofSilicon.com. External, third-party service providers operate such sites. Some of these sites will have their own separate membership processes and privacy policies. We do not control sites that are operated by others and are not responsible for the information practices of these sites. Other sites may set their own cookies, collect data or solicit personal information. It is always a good idea to check the privacy policy and terms of use of any site before offering any of your Personal Information. We do not share your Personal Information with these independent web sites. 

Information Storage and Security

Your Personal Information is stored on RopeofSilicon.com computer servers located in the United States. We protect your Personal Information with technical, administrative and physical safeguards to protect against loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification and improper disclosure. No computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard, but RopeofSilicon.com is committed to providing reasonable and appropriate security controls to protect RopeofSilicon.com and all Personal Information against foreseeable hazards. 

Notwithstanding these security measures, please be aware that when you submit Personal Information to RopeofSilicon.com over the Internet, the information may travel over many systems that are not under the RopeofSilicon.com's control. We take the protection of user data very seriously and to that end take reasonable safeguards to prevent interception of any Personal Information. 

Accessing, Correcting and Updating Your Information

To access, correct or update your account or other Personal Information such as your city or interests, please use the "Edit Profile Page" from your "User Home Page" by logging in to Your User Control Panel. 

If you have any other questions, comments or complaints about this Policy, please contact us via our online form, available at <http://www.ropeofsilicon.com/contact.php> or email us at: webmaster@ropeofsilicon.com. 

**Newsletters/E-Mail Alerts:** You may unsubscribe from email newsletters and alerts by following the instructions at the bottom of each newsletter or alert. 

**Email updates and special offers:** You may unsubscribe from email announcements by following the instructions at the bottom of each email. 

**Services:** You may unsubscribe to any service for which you have previously elected by following the instructions included in the RopeofSilicon.com [User Agreement](http://www.ropeofsilicon.com/useragreement/).  
  
---|---
